habitburger.com 2013-11-25

# Habit Burger » Privacy Policy

### Privacy Policy

**The Habit Burger Grill Privacy Policy**

**As used in this Privacy Policy, “The Habit Burger Grill” refers to all websites (including[http://www.habitburger.com](http://www.habitburger.com/)), properties, and services owned or operated by The Habit Burger Grill.**

**This Privacy Policy describes the privacy practices of The Habit Burger Grill. It explains when and how The Habit Burger Grill collects user information, how we use such information, and the circumstances under which we may disclose such information to others.**

**By visiting The Habit Burger Grill website, you acknowledge that you accept and consent to the practices outlined in this Privacy Policy.**

**What information do we collect?**

We collect information from you when you use our services, including visiting our website, placing an order, subscribing to our newsletter, responding to surveys or submitting forms. 

We may obtain the following types of information from you or concerning your computer or device, which may include information that can itself be used to identify and/or contact you (“Personally Identifiable Information”):

  * Name
  * Email Address
  * Mailing Address
  * Phone Number
  * Credit Card Information
  * Billing Address
  * Visitor Site Preferences

Google, as a third-party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on their visits to The Habit Burger Grill website and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy site <http://www.google.com/policies/technologies/ads/>. This Privacy Policy does not apply to Google, and Google’s ad and content network is not controlled or operated by The Habit Burger Grill.

**What do we use your information for?**

We use the information we collect in the following ways: 

_To personalize and enhance your experience._ We use the information we obtain from you, including Personally Identifiable Information, to register your account, fulfill your requests, understand your use of The Habit Burger Grill website, improve the website experience based on information and feedback we receive from you, and to personalize your experience on The Habit Burger Grill website.

_To process transactions._ We also use the information we obtain from you to process billing, fulfill orders, and provide customer service support.

_To communicate with our users._ We also use the information we obtain from you to communicate with you, including through our newsletters, and email, postal mail, text message, and telephone communications. By registering on our website or using our services, you specifically consent to the receipt of these communications. If you do not want to receive these communications from us, please follow the unsubscribe instructions in the body of such communications or e-mail [marketing@habitburger.com](mailto:marketing@habitburger.com).

_To administer contests, promotion, surveys or other site features._

**How do we protect your information?**

We have implemented reasonable security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order or enter, submit, or access your personal information. However, please keep in mind that no security system is impenetrable.

We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential.

**How do we protect your information from disclosure to third parties?**

Except as necessary to perform technical and administrative aspects of The Habit Burger Grill website (such as credit card processing or web hosting services), your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company, without your consent, other than as described in this Privacy Policy. The third parties that assist with performing technical and administrative aspects of the website are contractually obligated not to disclose or use your information for any other purpose, and to employ adequate security measures to prevent unauthorized access to such data. However, The Habit Burger Grill is not responsible in the event that your information is disclosed as a result of a breach or security lapse by any such third party.

The Habit Burger Grill also reserves the right to disclose any information to: (i) comply with any law, regulation or legal request; (ii) enforce and apply security policies; (iii) investigate breaches of the website’s security measures or any user agreements; or (iv) to protect the rights, property, user experience, or safety of The Habit Burger Grill, our employees, our users, or others.

If The Habit Burger Grill, or substantially all of its assets, is acquired by another company or successor entity, your information will be one of the assets transferred or acquired by the purchaser or successor. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any purchaser or successor to The Habit Burger Grill or its assets may continue to collect, use, and disclose your information acquired prior to such transfer or acquisition as set forth in this Privacy Policy.

**Do we use cookies?**

Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer’s hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information

We use cookies to keep track of advertisements and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business.

If you prefer, you can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies via your browser settings. Like most websites, if you turn your cookies off, some of our services may not function properly. However, you can still place orders over the telephone or by contacting customer service.

**California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

Because we value your privacy, we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent except as set forth in this Privacy Policy.

**Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

We are in compliance with the requirements of the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act. We do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

**Changes to our Privacy Policy**

We retain the discretion to amend or modify this Privacy Policy from time to time. If we make material changes to the way we collect, use or disclose Personally Identifying Information, we will notify you by posting a clear announcement on the website. Use and disclosure of information we obtain is subject to the current version of the Privacy Policy. Your continued access to or use of the website following constructive notice of material changes to this Privacy Policy shall constitute consent to any amendments and/or modifications.

The current version of the Privacy Policy can be found at <http://www.habitburger.com/privacy>.

**How to Contact Us**

We welcome any questions or comments about this Privacy Policy or our privacy practices. Any such comments or questions should be submitted via e-mail to [marketing@habitburger.com](mailto:marketing@habitburger.com).

**Effective Date of this Privacy Policy**

This Privacy Policy was last modified on March 28, 2013 and is effective as of that date.
